

MEASUM ALI HAIDER Business Developer Executive

(**-**) +923087226658

measuma816@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/measum-ali-haider/

(P) Lahore

(4) Male



Objective

Accomplished Business Development Professional with a proven history of success across diverse roles. As a Freelance Developer on Fiverr and Upwork, effectively managed multiple projects concurrently, showcasing strong project management skills. In the role of Business Development for CQ Technologies, played a pivotal role in managing client relationships and driving project teams. As a Business Development Manager at Python Technologies, demonstrated a strategic approach to generate new business, establish key relationships, and negotiate long-term agreements. Additionally, excelled in lead generation, resource acquisition, and client retention in positions with ReverbSoft Technologies and TechXpert. My comprehensive experience spans from technical expertise to impactful business growth strategies



Education

BS COMPUTER ENGINEERING

09/2016 - 10/2020

COMSATS Institute of Information Technology , Abbottabad



Work experience

BUSINESS DEVELOPMENT MANAGER

Sept 2023 - Present

Python Technologies (Remote Jobe)

- Manage Fiverr and Upwork Account
- Direct dealing with clients and closing deals
- Email marketing using different CRM
- Generating Leads through Linkedin sales navigator

SALES REPRESENTATIVE

July 2023 - Present

TechXpert (Remote Jobe)

- Manage Fiverr Accounts.
- Direct dealing with clients to close deals

FREELANCE DEVELOPER

Feb 2023 - Sept 2023

"Business development for CQ technologies Using email marketing and Linkedin sales navigator" reverbsoft experience

- Managed manyclients at the same time.
- Handled Projects and project teams.
- ♦ Done many projects of electronics, signal and system, image processing Usinng matlab.

DESIGN ENGINEER

04/2021 - 03/2022

Embedded extreme , Attock

- ♦ Lead a group of 3 phase signalgenerator using arduino.
- Design of simpleOp-Amp
- Design ofvariable power suppliesManage team of technitions

PS CORE CLOUD ENGINEER

04/2022 - 11/2022

Huawei , Islamabad

Good understanding of LTE(4G),UMTS (3G) and GSM (2G) Core EPC NetworkArchitectures, interfaces, nodes, KPIs, NFVIs and LLD.Supported in ATP casesTesting for new CloudEPCCore (CG,USN,CGW,DGW) in Ufone Network.

Huawei Cources & certificates:

- GPRSfundamental
- EPC fundamentals
- ❖ SAE networkprinciple
- **♦** USN9810
- **♦** UGW981
- ♦ 5GC (NSA & SA)
- TCP/IP subnetCCNA training

BUSINESS DEVELOPER EXECUTIVE

ReverbSoft Technologies ,Lahore

Responsibilities

- Lead Generation on Upwork and Freelancer
- Finding potential clients using
- LinkedIn Sales navigator
- Resourse aquisition and staffing
- Cold emailing



Achievements

5 new contracts withforeign people



Skills

♦ INTERPERSONAL Matlab Simulink , Python , AWSGoogle Cloud , MPLab Netbeans , SolidWorks LabView , MS office , MS excel Tool / Technology



Language

English

Urdu



Reference

Reference available on demand

Feb 2023- Sept 2023